{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Heating \u0026 Furnace Repair Contractors","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40076/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40076,"taskName":"Furnace / Forced Air Heating System - Repair or Service","taskDescription":"Repair or Service Furnace or Forced Air Heating System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Heating \u0026 Furnace Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":89,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"furnace forced air heat hvac","textMessagingName":"Svc Furnace","rolloverLongDesc":"This type of heating systems draws air from a few ducts around the home, heats it with some gas burners \u0026 then blows the warmed air back out through a separate, more extensive set of ducts.","rolloverShortDesc":"Also called forced air systems.  Very common type.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Furnace or Service Central Heating System. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Furnace \u0026 Heating Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Central Heating Maintenance","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Furnace - Repair or Service","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Furnace: Repair or Service","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Furnace Project","urlName":"Furnace-Forced-Air-Heating-System-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Furnace \u0026 Heating Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"furnace,forced,air,heat,hvac,central,baseboard,radiator,boiler,heaters,lamp,heat,vents,pump,ducts,radiant,hot,floor,wall,dehumidifying","emcCategoryOid":-12040,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":398,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40076/":{"taskOID":40076,"originalTaskOID":40076,"setID":398,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5550,"questionDisplayText":"Current Heating System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of central heating system do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10316,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10317,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane gas fired ","answerDisplayText":"Propane gas fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10318,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil fired","answerDisplayText":"Oil fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10319,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electric fired","answerDisplayText":"Electric fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5551,"questionDisplayText":"Problem with Heating System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why does your heating system need servicing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10161,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4305,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","answerDisplayText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4204,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No heat in one location","answerDisplayText":"No heat in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4203,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No heat in all locations","answerDisplayText":"No heat in all locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4685,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pilot light is out","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light is out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5818,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Smells funny","answerDisplayText":"Smells funny","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3725,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Makes odd noises","answerDisplayText":"Makes odd noises","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1974,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Doesn't get warm enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get warm enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1794,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","answerDisplayText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Runs constantly","answerDisplayText":"Runs constantly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6992,"questionDisplayText":"Age of Heating Equipment","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is your current heating system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10099,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10100,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10101,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5550,"questionDisplayText":"Current Heating System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of central heating system do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10316,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10317,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane gas fired ","answerDisplayText":"Propane gas fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10318,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil fired","answerDisplayText":"Oil fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10319,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electric fired","answerDisplayText":"Electric fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10316,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10317,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane gas fired ","answerDisplayText":"Propane gas fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10318,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil fired","answerDisplayText":"Oil fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10319,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electric fired","answerDisplayText":"Electric fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5551,"questionDisplayText":"Problem with Heating System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why does your heating system need servicing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10161,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4305,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","answerDisplayText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4204,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No heat in one location","answerDisplayText":"No heat in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4203,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No heat in all locations","answerDisplayText":"No heat in all locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4685,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pilot light is out","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light is out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5818,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Smells funny","answerDisplayText":"Smells funny","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3725,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Makes odd noises","answerDisplayText":"Makes odd noises","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1974,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Doesn't get warm enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get warm enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1794,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","answerDisplayText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Runs constantly","answerDisplayText":"Runs constantly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10161,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4305,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","answerDisplayText":"Nothing happens when it's turned on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4204,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No heat in one location","answerDisplayText":"No heat in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4203,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No heat in all locations","answerDisplayText":"No heat in all locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4685,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Pilot light is out","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light is out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5818,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Smells funny","answerDisplayText":"Smells funny","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3725,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Makes odd noises","answerDisplayText":"Makes odd noises","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1974,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Doesn't get warm enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get warm enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1794,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","answerDisplayText":"Cycles on/off too rapidly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Runs constantly","answerDisplayText":"Runs constantly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6992,"questionDisplayText":"Age of Heating Equipment","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is your current heating system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10099,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10100,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10101,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10099,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10100,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10101,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}